<dialogue>

<node>
<text>Step right up, wandering soul
</text>
</node>
<node>
<text>Where am I?
</text>
</node>
<node>
<text>What does the coin tell you?
</text>
</node>
<node>
<text>It whispers… Am I dead?
</text>
</node>
<node>
<text>Looks like your riches couldn’t save you.
</text>
</node>
<node>
<text>Get in and watch your step.
</text>
</node>
<node>
<text>Just hurry up and get me to the other side.
</text>
</node>
<node>
<text>How long does it take to get there?
</text>
</node>
<node>
<text>It depends on you
</text>
</node>
<node>
<text>What is this?
</text>
</node>
<node>
<text>Memories. Feelings. Something that prevents you from passing.
</text>
</node>
<node>
<text>Remember friendship? All those people, who helped you get to the top?
</text>
</node>
<node>
<text>I… I don’t. How could I forget?
</text>
</node>
<node>
<text>What about love? Does your memory treasure the moments you’ve spent with her?
</text>
</node>
<node>
<text>I do not remember! Why can’t I remember?
</text>
</node>
<node>
<text>Remember your son
</text>
</node>
<node>
<text>Stop.
</text>
</node>
<node>
<text>So you do remember him.
</text>
</node>
<node>
<text>Now I remember. There is no point in moving forward.
</text>
</node>
<node>
<text>No point in staying here either. Not only you’ll be trapped with this imagery
</text>
</node>
<node>
<text>But you’ll never get to the other side
</text>
</node>
<node>
<text>You will never achieve tranquility.
</text>
</node>
<node>
<text>Never will you escape the thought.
</text>
</node>
<node>
<text>Your son. What’s so special about him?
</text>
</node>
<node>
<text>He is my heir, the one, who now rules the empire I’ve built.
</text>
</node>
<node>
<text>So, is that why you’ve been cold to him? Your riches?
</text>
</node>
<node>
<text>That is not true! I’ve never done anything wrong to him!
</text>
</node>
<node>
<text>Right you are. You did absolutely nothing.
</text>
</node>
<node>
<text>You did not accept his affection.
</text>
</node>
<node>
<text>Not only he is now alone.
</text>
</node>
<node>
<text>He never was whole in a first place.
</text>
</node>
<node>
<text>But for some reason he gave you the coin.
</text>
</node>
<node>
<text>Enough! I get it! I get your signs, you monster!
</text>
</node>
<node>
<text>Get me back so i can undo my fdespicaple deeds!
</text>
</node>
<node>
<text>There is no way back to surface back there. Proceeding is only option.
</text>
</node>
<node>
<text>Now swallow your false pride and advance.
</text>
</node>
<node>
<text>So in the end he gave me the coin?
</text>
</node>
<node>
<text>He came to the grave your corpse is in.
</text>
</node>
<node>
<text>Alone at the site. Silent wheeping.
</text>
</node>
<node>
<text>That is what he gave to the soul of his father.
</text>
</node>
<node>
<text>Not even a tear. But a little bit of sorrow, transformed in a little copper coin.
</text>
</node>
<node>
<text>And even that was stolen by you.
</text>
</node>
<node>
<text>Not only you stole his father’s name and killed his love.
</text>
</node>
<node>
<text>Not only you’ve murdered him and claimed his newborn son as your own.
</text>
</node>
<node>
<text>You couldn’t just spare him a coin in the afterlife.
</text>
</node>
<node>
<text>We’re almost there, but I do not work for free.
</text>
</node>
<node>
<text>And apparently you have no money.
</text>
</node>
<node>
<text>No, you can’t get me all the way back! We’re almost there!
</text>
</node>
<node>
<text>You are not getting back.
</text>
</node>
<node>
<text>The coin will get back to his owner when his time will come.
</text>
</node>
</dialogue>